<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<link rel="self" href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/" />
	<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/</id>
	<title>Andrés Gorzelany</title>
	<rights>2019</rights>
	<updated>2019-08-21T13:45:11Z</updated>
	<subtitle>Microsoft Senior Consultant</subtitle>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/teams-retention-policies" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/teams-retention-policies</id>
		<title>New-RetentionCompliancePolicy and Teams</title>
		<updated>2019-08-21T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/mugatu.PNG" class="img-fluid" alt="teamsSoHot" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a nice post &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/Microsoft-Teams-Blog/Retention-policies-for-Microsoft-Teams/ba-p/178011"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;
explaining how Retention policies for Microsoft Teams work, the intention of this blog post is not to talk about that but is kinda a
quick cheat sheet if you happen to use the New-RetentionCompliancePolicy cmdlet for Teams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New-RetentionCompliancePolicy includes four parameters related to Teams:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;TeamsChannelLocation&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The TeamsChannelLocation parameter is used to target specific Teams to include in the policy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;TeamsChannelLocationException&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This parameter specifies the Teams to exclude when you use the value All for the TeamsChannelLocation parameter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;TeamsChatLocation&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The TeamsChatLocation parameter is used to target specific Teams users to include in the policy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;TeamsChatLocationException&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This parameter specifies the Teams users to exclude when you use the value All for the TeamsChatLocation parameter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="now-some-examples"&gt;Now, some examples:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="example-1"&gt;Example 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;New-RetentionCompliancePolicy -Name &amp;quot;Example1&amp;quot; -TeamsChannelLocation &amp;quot;All&amp;quot; -TeamsChannelLocationException &amp;quot;32996b0b-67f6-4159-b4bf-f738d12a5f86&amp;quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this example the Retention applies to all Teams except the Team with GUID 32996b0b-67f6-4159-b4bf-f738d12a5f86, we can only specify an
Exception when &amp;quot;All&amp;quot; is used for the location parameter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="example-2"&gt;Example 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;New-RetentionCompliancePolicy -Name &amp;quot;Example2&amp;quot; -TeamsChannelLocation &amp;quot;operations&amp;#64;M365x71714.onmicrosoft.com&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;systems&amp;#64;M365x71714.onmicrosoft.com&amp;quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this example the Retention applies to the Teams operations and systems, as you can see, we are specifying the Teams with email address.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="example-3"&gt;Example 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;New-RetentionCompliancePolicy -Name &amp;quot;Example3&amp;quot; -TeamsChatLocation &amp;quot;All&amp;quot; -TeamsChatLocationException
 &amp;quot;Allan Deyoung&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;Cameron White&amp;quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this example the Retention applies to all users except Allan and Cameron, see that we are specifying them with their Name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="example-4"&gt;Example 4&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;New-RetentionCompliancePolicy -Name &amp;quot;Example4&amp;quot; -TeamsChatLocation &amp;quot;41f18a1c-2e21-4c6c-bca9-3b51a8d18a80&amp;quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this example the Retention applies only to user with id 41f18a1c-2e21-4c6c-bca9-3b51a8d18a80, see that we are specifying them with their id
we can get this id thru Azure AD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can specify Teams with their name, email, guid and users with their name, email, DN and guid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="one-more-thing"&gt;One more thing...&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing I noticed, is that, policies created using Powershell can't be edited later using the Office 365 Security &amp;amp; Compliance portal, hope
Microsoft fix this soon.
Also, if you use &lt;a href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/module/exchange/policy-and-compliance-retention/get-retentioncompliancepolicy?view=exchange-ps"&gt;Get-RetentionCompliancePolicy&lt;/a&gt;
to retrieve the newly created policies, you will notice that these attributes will be empty:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;TeamsChatLocation             : {}

TeamsChatLocationException    : {}

TeamsChannelLocation          : {}

TeamsChannelLocationException : {}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reason for that is that you need to use the -DistributionDetail parameter with it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;TeamsChatLocation             : {Debra Berger, Allan Deyoung}
TeamsChatLocationException    : {}
TeamsChannelLocation          : {}
TeamsChannelLocationException : {}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope this is useful for somebody.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/mugatu.PNG" class="img-fluid" alt="teamsSoHot"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/spmt-module" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/spmt-module</id>
		<title>The specified module 'Microsoft.SharePoint.MigrationTool.PowerShell' was not loaded because no valid module file was found in any module directory</title>
		<updated>2019-07-17T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully, this is only useful temporarily until it is fixed in the installation package, but currently, if you install the &lt;a href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/sharepointmigration/introducing-the-sharepoint-migration-tool"&gt;Sharepoint Migration Tool&lt;/a&gt;
module files will be copied to &lt;code&gt;$env:UserProfile\Documents\WindowsPowerShell\Modules\Microsoft.SharePoint.MigrationTool.PowerShell&lt;/code&gt; as the &lt;a href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/sharepointmigration/overview-spmt-ps-cmdlets"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But if you try to import the module, you will receive an error:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;PS C:\Users\user\Documents\WindowsPowerShell\Modules\Microsoft.SharePoint.MigrationTool.PowerShell&amp;gt; Import-Module Mi
crosoft.SharePoint.MigrationTool.PowerShell
Import-Module : The specified module 'Microsoft.SharePoint.MigrationTool.PowerShell' was not loaded because no
valid module file was found in any module directory.
At line:1 char:1
+ Import-Module Microsoft.SharePoint.MigrationTool.PowerShell
+ ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
    + CategoryInfo          : ResourceUnavailable: (Microsoft.Share...Tool.PowerShell:String) [Import-Module], File
   NotFoundException
    + FullyQualifiedErrorId : Modules_ModuleNotFound,Microsoft.PowerShell.Commands.ImportModuleCommand
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Simply copy the &lt;code&gt;Microsoft.SharePoint.MigrationTool.PowerShell&lt;/code&gt; folder in &lt;code&gt;C:\Program Files\WindowsPowerShell\Modules&lt;/code&gt; and you will be able to import it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/Export-TFSReleaseDefinitions" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/Export-TFSReleaseDefinitions</id>
		<title>Export TFS Release Definitions to a CSV file</title>
		<updated>2019-05-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I created a simple small script in Powershell to query Team Foundation Server to get a list of all Release Definitions per project, the
output of the script is a csv file with this header&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;quot;Project;ReleaseDefinition&amp;quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It uses the REST API to query for this information and if the project does not have release definition it will appear with a NULL value on
the ReleaseDefinition column, only one time of course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="input-parameters"&gt;Input parameters&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It asks for FQDN, CollectionName and Path for the CSV file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="current-limitations"&gt;Current limitations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was only tested against Team Foundation Server 2017, I expect to improve it including more versions.
Have to change the way the FQDN is asked, as http is currently hard-coded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full script can be found here &lt;a href="https://github.com/get-itips/AzureDevopsTools/blob/master/azuredevopstools-ps/Export-TFSReleaseDefinitions.ps1"&gt;Export-TFSReleaseDefinitions.ps1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/sfbonprem-interpretedusertype" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/sfbonprem-interpretedusertype</id>
		<title>SfB On-Prem decommission and InterpretedUserType</title>
		<updated>2019-05-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/DeploymentLocator.png" class="img-fluid" alt="msRTCSip-DeploymentLocator" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi!
I was involved in a project with my colleage &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/dariomws"&gt;Dario Woitasen&lt;/a&gt; to remove Skype for Business from an hybrid deployment with SfB Online and experienced some odd things that we had to deal with.
I want to share them if anyone experiences the same as we did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a start, we followed this excellent guide &lt;a href="https://blogs.technet.microsoft.com/fasttracktips/2017/06/27/decommissioning-skypelync-on-premises/"&gt;Decommissioning Skype/Lync on-premises&lt;/a&gt; but, as usual, as we progressed we saw that there were more things to take into account.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the steps includes running this cmdlet for all users&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disable-CsUser&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, this cmdlet should:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear all msRTCSip- attributes of every enabled user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But actually:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did not fully clear the msRTCSip- attributes, specially msRTCSip-DeploymentLocator, more info on this attrib &lt;a href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/skypeforbusiness/schema-reference/active-directory-schema-extensions-classes-and-attributes/schema-attributes-and-descriptions"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removed sip:user&amp;#64;contoso.com from proxyAddresses attribute!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This lead to two things:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Single sign-on stopped working for the SfB client&lt;/strong&gt;, later, we identified that this was caused by the sip:user&amp;#64;contoso.com entry not being present in proxyAddresses (remember that Disable-CsUser deleted this?), so we created a script to fix this in local AD domain:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;$csv=import-csv &amp;quot;D:\Users.csv&amp;quot;

foreach($user in $csv){
        $userUpn=$user.SipAddress.Replace(&amp;quot;sip:&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;&amp;quot;)
        #Do not add proxyAddress if it is present already
        $proxies=Get-ADUser -Filter &amp;quot;UserPrincipalName -eq '$userupn'&amp;quot; -properties * | Select-Object &amp;#64;{Name=“proxyAddresses”;Expression={$_.proxyAddresses}}


        if(($null -eq $proxies) -or ($proxies.proxyAddresses -join ' ' -notmatch &amp;quot;sip:&amp;quot;)) #empty list of ProxyAddresses
        {
            write-host &amp;quot;Adding sip&amp;quot;
            Get-ADUser -Filter &amp;quot;UserPrincipalName -eq '$userupn'&amp;quot; | Set-ADUser -Add &amp;#64;{&amp;quot;proxyAddresses&amp;quot;=$user.SipAddress}
        }
        else
        {
            write-host &amp;quot;No need to Add sip&amp;quot;
        }
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look that this is a portion of the real script, that is reading a csv file with the output of users that need to be treated, csv has a column for the User's Sip Address exported from SfB Online Powershell, like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-c"&gt;&amp;quot;SipAddress&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;sip:debrab&amp;#64;contoso.com&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;sip:johnd&amp;#64;contoso.com&amp;quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once we added this attribute to the local AD, &lt;em&gt;single sign-on worked again&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where were we? oh yes... the presence of values in msRTCSip-DeploymentLocator attribute in the local Active Directory lead to the SfB Online deployment (after Azure AD Sync) to &amp;quot;think&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;interpret&amp;quot; that the users were still hybrid or OnPrem and this prevented (or at least we feared) to remove the last on-prem servers.
We concluded this looking at the InterpretedUserType of the users and in the process, we identified all of these possible values for  an SfB Online user account:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-c"&gt;DirSyncDisabledDisabledUser
DirSyncDisabledNoService
DirSyncDisabledSfBUser
DirSyncDisabledUser
DirSyncNoService
DirSyncSfBUser
DirSyncSfBUserNeedsProvisioning
HybridOnlineDisabledUser
HybridOnlineDisabledUserNeedsProvisioning
HybridOnlineDisabledUserWithDeletedLicenses
HybridOnlineSfBUser
HybridOnlineSfBUserWithDeletedLicenses
HybridOnpremDisabledUser
HybridOnpremSfBUser
PureOnlineNoService
PureOnlineNoServiceWithDeletedLicenses
PureOnlineSfBUser
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are not sure of the complete enumeration of this type of data, but as you may see, the list is big, this excellent post tries to explain some of them &lt;a href="http://www.be-com.eu/?p=3286"&gt;InterpretedUserType to the rescue for Hybrid Deployments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="interpretedusertype"&gt;InterpretedUserType&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We could not find official documentation about the exact meaning of every value, so I will try to match them to other values I observed, so please use this at your own risk, if I found out that some of this values is incorrect or get any official documentation I will update this&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DirSyncDisabledDisabledUser&lt;/strong&gt;: User account disabled in SfB online and disabled in local AD, has a sipAddress attribute online, RegistrarPool has a value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DirSyncDisabledNoService&lt;/strong&gt;: User account disabled in SfB online and does not have a sipAddress attribute online, RegistrarPool empty, OnPremHostingProvider shows sipfed.online.lync.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DirSyncDisabledSfBUser&lt;/strong&gt;: User account disabled in SfB online and has a sipAddress attribute online, also, has a RegistrarPool value and OnPremHostingProvider is empty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DirSyncDisabledUser&lt;/strong&gt;: User account disabled in SfB online and disabled in local AD, does not have a RegistrarPool value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DirSyncNoService&lt;/strong&gt;: To this day, I still do not know exactly what that means.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DirSyncSfBUser&lt;/strong&gt;: Enabled in SfB Online, has a SipAddress and has a RegistrarPool, this is the best value we can get.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DirSyncSfBUserNeedsProvisioning&lt;/strong&gt;: This appears to be a temporal state before DirSyncSfBUser&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HybridOnlineDisabledUser&lt;/strong&gt;: User account disabled in SfB online, has a SipAddress attribute online and OnPremHostingProvider is not empty.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HybridOnlineDisabledUserNeedsProvisioning&lt;/strong&gt;: User account disabled in SfB online, hasn't a SipAddress attribute online and OnPremHostingProvider is not empty.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HybridOnlineDisabledUserWithDeletedLicenses&lt;/strong&gt;: It's like HybridOnlineDisabledUser but, it seems that license is not assigned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HybridOnlineSfBUser&lt;/strong&gt;: User account enabled and DirSynched, has a SipAddress and a OnPremHostingProvider and RegistrarPool.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HybridOnlineSfBUserWithDeletedLicenses&lt;/strong&gt;: Same as HybridOnlineSfBUser but judging by the name, it seems that license is not present.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HybridOnpremDisabledUser&lt;/strong&gt;: User account disabled in SfB OnPrem, OnPremHostingProvider has &amp;quot;SRV:&amp;quot; value and RegistrarPool is empty.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HybridOnpremSfBUser&lt;/strong&gt;: According to Johan Delimon's Blog, the account is created at Customer AD, DirSynched and uses SfB OnPrem, we can judge this by the presence of OnPremHostingProvider&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PureOnlineNoService&lt;/strong&gt;: I still do not know exactly what that means.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PureOnlineNoServiceWithDeletedLicenses&lt;/strong&gt;: User account created in Office 365, has no local AD account, so is not DirSynched, has no SfB license.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PureOnlineSfBUser&lt;/strong&gt;: User account created in Office 365, has no local AD account, so is not DirSynched, and uses SfB Online.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, as I said, &lt;em&gt;Disable-CsUser&lt;/em&gt; did not clear the &lt;em&gt;msRTCSIP-DeploymentLocator&lt;/em&gt; value, this lead to having most of the users in an undesired state. OnPremHostingProvider is an Online attribute that is synced with it, for more information, see &lt;a href="http://toregj.blogspot.com/2017/03/skype-online-user-is-disabled-although.html"&gt;Skype Online user is disabled, although Skype Online license assigned!&lt;/a&gt; so we first cleared all the msRTCSIP- attributes in local AD for a user and waited for sync... when synced happened, we observe the attribute InterpretedUserType changing for example from HybridOnlineSfbUser to DirSyncSfBUserNeedsProvisioning until it went to the final state DirSyncSfBUser, but for this, we had to wait hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, we created an script to clear all msRTCSIP- for every user in local Active Directory domain:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;#ok lets clear msRTCSIP-* Attributes
        write-host &amp;quot;Clearing msRTCSIP-* Attributes&amp;quot;
        Get-ADUser -Filter &amp;quot;UserPrincipalName -eq '$userupn'&amp;quot; | Set-ADUser -clear msRTCSIP-ApplicationOptions,msRTCSIP-DeploymentLocator,msRTCSIP-Line,msRTCSIP-OwnerUrn,msRTCSIP-PrimaryUserAddress,msRTCSIP-UserEnabled,msRTCSIP-OptionFlags
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(I recommend running this cmdlet against the same Domain Controller using the -Server parameter)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's it, we waited some hours and started to see the expected value for the users (DirSyncSfBUser), then, we followed the guide and removed the last servers and ran Disable-CsAdDomain and Disable-CsAdForest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope this post helps anyone that stumble upon the same scenario as Dario and me got.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/DeploymentLocator.png" class="img-fluid" alt="msRTCSip-DeploymentLocator"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/PwshGitHubTools" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/PwshGitHubTools</id>
		<title>It's like SysInternals, but for Git-Hub!</title>
		<updated>2019-03-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;Hi!
(Well... If the great Mark Russinovich allows me... obviously)
I am back! It's been a busy year, hopefully, I'll write more often.
Last year I started contributing in GitHub, more specifically as a Collaborator for docs.microsoft.com creating Pull Requests to improve the documentation based on user feedback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me tell you that is an activity I really enjoy to do! I think Microsoft has made the right choice open-sourcing the documentation of their solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So as I am a PowerShell guy (now a PowerShell Core guy) I created a small script to check the status of Issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The name of this Script is Get-GitHubIssuesState.ps1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example Use&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;PS &amp;gt; .\Get-GitHubIssuesState.ps1 -Owner MicrosoftDocs -Repo officedocs-SkypeForBusiness -Issues 834,817,803,779,777,772,771,774,663 -OAuthtoken x02ab2e5xxx34ef25fea707cfb02542e9d7xxx
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The reason behind needing OAuthToken is because of a limit in requests per hour that an anonymous user can make.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The repo is located &lt;a href="https://github.com/get-itips/PwshGitHubTools"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and I expect to create other small tools to do things with GitHub through PowerShell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, PowerShell makes you PowerFULL&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;Hi!
(Well... If the great Mark Russinovich allows me... obviously)
I am back! It's been a busy year, hopefully, I'll write more often.
Last year I started contributing in GitHub, more specifically as a Collaborator for docs.microsoft.com creating Pull Requests to improve the documentation based on user feedback.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/cannot-lock" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/cannot-lock</id>
		<title>Error cannot lock ref Git fetch failed with exit code 1 unable to update local ref</title>
		<updated>2018-09-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had to troubleshoot this error on one of my customers and wanted to share so if anyone encounter this can use this solution.
Basically, when executing a Build using TFS Build Agents, we were seeing this error&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;2018-09-17T19:10:10.9599867Z  * [new branch]        ABZ-Branch -&amp;gt; origin/ABZ-Branch
2018-09-17T19:10:10.9599867Z error: cannot lock ref 'refs/remotes/origin/Abz-Branch': is at 551a179d8451f1154e0b38b85993a439d8c39af2 but expected e887cf2f4e449bd480560b8aee827bf140faf65a
2018-09-17T19:10:10.9599867Z  ! e887cf2f..087dcca9  Abz-Branch -&amp;gt; origin/Abz-Branch  (unable to update local ref)
2018-09-17T19:10:11.0381160Z ##[error]Git fetch failed with exit code: 1
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strange huh? if you do a search you won't find exactly this error, on similar situations we can recommendations to do a git prune, but I did this with no luck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I saw something, as you can see in the extracted log, there is ABZ-Branch and Abz-Branch, they might seem the same branch but they are different in case!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TFS, at least 2017 update 3 is not preventing you from creating branches with the same name but different case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Git install where the Build agents are, is not making difference of this, so it is not case sensitive, (as digging into Agent's work folder at for example&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;E:\Agents\Agent01\_work\2\s\.git\config
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;you can see there that&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;ignorecase = true
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;so it is processing the git fetch as if ABZ-Branch and Abz-Branch were the same! leading  to the error saying that it is expecting other digest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if you encounter exactly this, check if you have two branches with the same name but different case.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/ScriptPoshLTM" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/ScriptPoshLTM</id>
		<title>Script to call POSH-LTM-Rest cmdlets to enable or disable Pool Members on a F5 LTM Load Balancer</title>
		<updated>2018-03-21T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had to do this PS Script for a customer, they use TFS and wanted to control F5 LTM (Load Balancer) to disable or enable nodes in a release definition,
so they can disable a node, update the binaries on it, and enable it again.
So, I found this excellent &lt;a href="https://github.com/joel74/POSH-LTM-Rest"&gt;Powershell modules&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href="https://github.com/joel74"&gt;Joel74&lt;/a&gt; that include the needed functions.
First of all, you have to install the POSH-LTM modules as the creator says on his github page on the computer that will be used to run the PS Script,
then, save this PS Script on the same computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt; param (
    [Parameter(Mandatory=$true)][string]$LTMName,
    [Parameter(Mandatory=$true)][string]$Partition,
    [Parameter(Mandatory=$true)][string]$PoolName,
    [Parameter(Mandatory=$true)][string]$MemberName,
    [switch]$disable = $false,
    [Parameter(Mandatory=$true)][string]$F5Username,
    [Parameter(Mandatory=$true)][string]$F5Password
)

$passwd = $F5Password
$user=$F5Username

$secpasswd = ConvertTo-SecureString $passwd -AsPlainText -Force
$ltmCreds = New-Object System.Management.Automation.PSCredential ($user, $secpasswd)


#Se solicita una sesion al F5 BIG-IP
$session = $null
$session = New-F5Session -LTMCredentials $ltmCreds -LTMName $LTMName -PassThrough

if($session -ne $null){
    if($Disable){
    Write-Verbose &amp;quot;Trying to disable $LTMName|$Partition|$PoolName|$MemberName&amp;quot;
    Disable-PoolMember -F5Session $session -PoolName $PoolName -Partition $Partition -Name $MemberName

    }else{
    Write-Verbose &amp;quot;Trying to enable $LTMName|$Partition|$PoolName|$MemberName&amp;quot;
    Enable-PoolMember -F5Session $session -PoolName $PoolName -Partition $Partition -Name $MemberName
    }
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go to the release definition of your project of choice, and add a &amp;quot;Powershell on target Machines&amp;quot; task, fill the fields as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Machines: fill with the hostname or IP of the computer with the PS Module and PS Script saved in the last step.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Admin Login / Password: Credentials to connect to this computer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protocol: HTTP or HTTPS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Powershell Script: Full path to the PS Script saved in the last step, for example C:\Scripts\F5Manage-TeamMember.ps1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Script Arguments: Arguments needed by my script, for example, using release variables:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-LTMName $(LTMName) -Partition $(Partition) -PoolName $(PoolName) -MemberName $(MemberName) -F5Username $(Username) -F5Password $(Password)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to create this variables in the release definition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Test it. always test it on your environment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/open-office-fiasco" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/open-office-fiasco</id>
		<title>The Open Office Space is a fiasco</title>
		<updated>2018-02-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;This time I took the liberty of talking about something that it is not IT related, but it is work related, here it goes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some years now, we saw a new trend in offices, &amp;quot;let's remove the cubicles&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;let's remove the walls&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;this way, we can be more productive&amp;quot;.
Ok, the intention was good but, as a consultant that visits many companies I observed (and suffered) some things about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, you feel in a jungle, you hear multiple people talking, even on top of your own voice in your head, you loose focus if you need to concentrate, in this jungle, you will find people that is either yelling to someone on the phone, listening to their favourite music, making jokes to their partner or whatever that does not have anything to do with your job, so you maybe start to use headphones, a thing that is not always possible in every situation or if it is, the people on the office will surely start to think that you have some kind of social relationship problem, &amp;quot;hey, here comes that weird solo-guy&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another thing that happens in this jungle is constant interruption of your work: &amp;quot;hey, didn't send you an email because I saw you that we were in the same floor, please stop what you are doing right now and see my big little problem, come on, I also brought to you my notebook to your desk&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why? why office designers did you have to do this? did you even work in an office before? did you experience your great idea before releasing it to the world? or are you testing the beta version of it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not saying that we must return to the cubicle maze, but hey, let's find something in between of that, maybe we can have a more classic area and an open area in the same building so people can choose where they are more productive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My two cents on this. I really want to know what is your opinion&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;This time I took the liberty of talking about something that it is not IT related, but it is work related, here it goes:&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/call-failed" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/call-failed</id>
		<title>Call failed to establish due to a media connectivity failure when both endpoints are...</title>
		<updated>2017-07-21T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;internal&lt;br /&gt;
external&lt;br /&gt;
or one endpoint is internal and the other is federated or remote...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;any situation will do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was happening to me on an On-Premise deployment of Skype For Business (Front end and Edge Server) calling to Unified Messaging contact on Exchange Online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ICE Candidate negotiation was happening but eventually no &lt;code&gt;remote-candidates&lt;/code&gt; were negotiated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-cmd"&gt;ms-client-diagnostics: 22; reason=&amp;quot;Call failed to establish due to a media connectivity failure when both endpoints are internal&amp;quot;;UserType=&amp;quot;Callee&amp;quot;;MediaType=&amp;quot;audio&amp;quot;;MediaChanBlob=&amp;quot;NetworkErr=no error,ErrTime=0,RTPSeq=0,SeqDelta=0,RTPTime=0,RTCPTime=0,TransptRecvErr=0x0,RecvErrTime=0,TransptSendErr=0x0,SendErrTime=0,InterfacesStall=0x0,InterfacesConnCheck=0x0,MediaTimeout=0,RtcpByeSent=0,RtcpByeRcvd=0,BlobVer=1&amp;quot;;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this must be firewall-related, this is almost always firewall-related, it seems first that the NAT was maybe responding with another external IP from de ISP Pool, but that was ok, the rules were correct, we checked and re-rechecked, and after so many hours of troubleshooting with Snooper and Wireshark, we started to look more deeply on the firewall and tried weird things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The firewall, a Fortigate one, had a NAT button enabled on the rule, you would say, that is obvious that must be activated... but we tried and deactivated that and... Voilá! we saw the face of god at that moment, it worked, the remote-candidates were negotiated at that moment  (so always be sure that this line is present if you want to know that it is working ok)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-cmd"&gt;a=remote-candidates:1 65.55.127.80 54860 2 65.55.127.80 54721
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and we lived happily ever after.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;internal&lt;br&gt;
external&lt;br&gt;
or one endpoint is internal and the other is federated or remote...&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/csv-adPerm" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/csv-adPerm</id>
		<title>Powershell Script to CSV all AD Permissions for a particular Receive Connector</title>
		<updated>2017-02-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had to do this PS Script for me to troubleshoot a receive connector permissions problem.
This will output to a CSV all permissions assigned to a receive connector, please change the $path and $connector variables to suit your needs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;$path = &amp;quot;E:\path\dumpRights.csv&amp;quot;
$csv = &amp;quot;user,identity,deny,accessrights,extendedrights`r`n&amp;quot;
$connector=&amp;quot;connectorName&amp;quot;
$perms=Get-adpermission $connector

foreach($perm in $perms){
    $perm
    $csv+=$perm.user.RawIdentity+ &amp;quot;,&amp;quot; + $perm.identity.ToString() + &amp;quot;,&amp;quot; + $perm.deny.IsPresent + &amp;quot;,&amp;quot; + $perm.accessrights + &amp;quot;,&amp;quot; + $perm.extendedrights
    $csv +=&amp;quot;`n&amp;quot;
}

$fso = new-object -comobject scripting.filesystemobject
$file = $fso.CreateTextFile($path,$true)
$file.write($csv)
$file.close()
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/handy-handshake" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/handy-handshake</id>
		<title>Handy SMTP Handshake for testing with Telnet</title>
		<updated>2017-02-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's always useful to test SMTP service, using Telnet, so these are the commands needed:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, connect through Command Prompt or Powershell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-cmd"&gt;Telnet x.x.x.x tcpPort
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Example &lt;code&gt;Telnet 10.0.2.1 25&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will get a welcome message from SMTP Server, like this one:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;220 exc02.contoso.com Microsoft ESMTP MAIL Service ready at Wed&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;then write sequentially hitting enter at each line what is coloured in green here (no color lines are server responses)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-code"&gt;EHLO mailtesting
AUTH LOGIN
334 VXNlcm5hbWU6
Y29udG9zb1xhY2NvdW50
334 UGFzc3dvcmQ6
dGhlUGFzc3dvcmQ=
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-code"&gt;MAIL FROM:
RCPT TO:
DATA
Subject: here comes the test 
This is the email content.
.
250 Queued mail for delivery 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important notes:&lt;/strong&gt;
You have to hit enter twice after subject input.
account name and password are entered Base64 encoded, so first encode that information using for example &lt;a href="https://www.base64encode.org/"&gt;this site.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/import-ca-trend-iwsva" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/import-ca-trend-iwsva</id>
		<title>How to succesfully import Root CA to Trend IWSVA</title>
		<updated>2016-12-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;Customer reached me to get help importing Root CA certificate to InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance,&lt;br /&gt;
from Trend Micro documentation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="blockquote"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;By default, IWSVA acts as a private Certificate Authority (CA) and dynamically generates digital certificates&lt;br /&gt;
that are sent to client browsers to complete a secure passage for HTTPS connections. However, the default CA
is not signed by a well-known (trusted) CA on the Internet.Client browsers always display a certificate
warning every time users access an HTTPS Web site.
Although users can safely ignore the certificate warning, Trend Micro recommends using a signed root certificate for IWSVA.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, if you want your users not to receive a warning from their browsers you have to use, typical,an internal Certification Authority that all client computers trust, for example an Enterprise Windows CA like this was the case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, first of all, I had to export the CA Root Certificate including the Private Key,&lt;br /&gt;
go on and logon the Certification Authority computer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go to 'Start' -&amp;gt; 'Run' -&amp;gt; mmc.exe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on 'File' -&amp;gt; 'Add / Remove Snap-in'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click the 'Add...' button&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select 'Certificates' then click 'Add'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select 'Computer Account' -&amp;gt; 'Next' -&amp;gt; 'Local Computer' -&amp;gt; 'Finish'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;click 'Close' -&amp;gt; 'OK'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expand Certificates -&amp;gt; and click on 'Personal' -&amp;gt; 'Certificates'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Right click the CA cert and choose 'All Tasks' -&amp;gt; 'Export'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click 'Next' -&amp;gt; Select 'Yes, Export the private key' -&amp;gt; 'Next'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uncheck all of the options here. PKCS 12 should be the only option available. Click 'Next'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give the private key a password of your choice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give a filename to save as and click 'Next', then 'Finish'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that you have a .pfx file we will need to use the excellent tool called OpenSSL, as I was using Windows, I used OpenSSL for Windows binaries that you can get here &lt;a href="http://gnuwin32.sourceforge.net/packages/openssl.htm"&gt;http://gnuwin32.sourceforge.net/packages/openssl.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Install it and copy the pfx to your computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;start a command prompt or PowerShell and run:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-cmd"&gt;openssl pkcs12 -in -clcerts -nokeys -out certificate.cer
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;then&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-cmd"&gt;openssl pkcs12 -in -nocerts -out pkey-encrypted.key 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will end up with two files: certificate.cer and pkey-encrypted.key&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you import them right into IWSVA console it will fail saying &amp;quot;Root Certificate file is invalid. Try Again&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This drove me nuts, documentation is not so good, it only says you need to provide a PEM file format,  base54 encoded and RSA based encrypted key, and I was sure I was providing just that...  but wait... after many tries and errors, I read that some systems do not accept anything below this line in public certificate key file:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-code"&gt;-----BEGIN CERTIFICATE-----
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and this line for the private key file&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-code"&gt;-----BEGIN PRIVATE KEY-----
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;so I tried and deleted everything below that lines on both lines... and it worked! Apparently IWSVA can not handle well ignoring the information that comes there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope is useful for someone else.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;Customer reached me to get help importing Root CA certificate to InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance,&lt;br&gt;
from Trend Micro documentation:&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/workflow-manager-error" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/workflow-manager-error</id>
		<title>Workflow Manager Re-Registration despite everything seems ok</title>
		<updated>2016-11-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;So,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you did the exact steps and you receive the &amp;quot;Workflow is connected&amp;quot; message when you click on Workflow Manager Service Application inside Sharepoint Central Admin, but somehow, something is not working quite right, or maybe you receive this message trying to publish in Sharepoint Designer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/workflowmgr_error.png" class="img-fluid" alt="WorkFlow Manager Error" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Solution: Re-Register the Workflow Service using Register-SPWorkflowService and the -Force Parameter. There is a good chance everything starts working then.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;So,&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/limit-dw-ignite-videos" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/limit-dw-ignite-videos</id>
		<title>How to limit download rate on Ignite Videos</title>
		<updated>2016-10-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;If you are using &lt;a href="http://tomtalks.uk/2015/05/download-all-the-skype-for-business-ignite-sessions/"&gt;THE powershell&lt;/a&gt; script to download Ignite 2016 Videos and Slide Decks you probably noticed that it will try to use all your bandwidth available and maybe kill all your connections, so, if this happened to you, you will find this useful&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hack into the ps file, go to line 156:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;Start-Process -FilePath .\youtube-dl.exe -ArgumentList &amp;quot;-o &amp;quot;&amp;quot;$vidFullFile&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;, $url -NoNewWindow -Wait
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and replace with this&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;Start-Process -FilePath .\youtube-dl.exe -ArgumentList &amp;quot;-o &amp;quot;&amp;quot;$vidFullFile&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;--limit-rate 30K&amp;quot; , $url -NoNewWindow -Wait
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;customize the --limit-rate argument to suit your preferences and voila!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;If you are using &lt;a href="http://tomtalks.uk/2015/05/download-all-the-skype-for-business-ignite-sessions/"&gt;THE powershell&lt;/a&gt; script to download Ignite 2016 Videos and Slide Decks you probably noticed that it will try to use all your bandwidth available and maybe kill all your connections, so, if this happened to you, you will find this useful&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/ignite-2016" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/ignite-2016</id>
		<title>IGNITE 2016 IS GONE… LONG LIVE THE KING!</title>
		<updated>2016-10-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;Ignite 2016 has finished and it was an intensive, useful great experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you experienced the same as us, you can not get to all the sessions, the conference center was big enough to &lt;strong&gt;walk an average of 12 kilometers a day&lt;/strong&gt; (nearly 8 miles) and, I am not joking, it’s true, Google Fit told me everyday, so, the first day you get a little frustrated walking fast to go from one place to another, but the second or third day you realize the truth, and start to watch some sessions from hangouts or just sit anywhere and get the streaming using some headphones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, wait, what about if you couldn’t make it to Atlanta this year? no problem, or at least, you can get the juice of the sessions and slide decks using &lt;a href="http://tomtalks.uk/2015/05/download-all-the-skype-for-business-ignite-sessions/"&gt;this Powershell Script&lt;/a&gt;  to download them all (or maybe download the ones you are interested in), you can select the quality of the sessions too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lessons learned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As I told, you can not get to all the sessions, do not try, but, you have other options.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Try to avoid sessions on Expo, is a little difficult to hear the speaker as people walks by around you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner lead sessions are good to have real life situations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sessions lead by Microsoft Gurus like Jeffrey Snover and Mark Russinovich are a must-attend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use sneakers, you will have to walk A LOT&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do Networking, do it, talk to people, they do the same things as you do, they work on IT, it’s an excellent opportunity to share experiences and maybe to do business!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Ignite ends, your work starts, you will have to review what you have learned in the sessions, get deep on them and apply to your everyday work to grow your ITPro knowledge, maybe it’s a chosen certification path, maybe new solutions to offer to your customers, in other words, capitalize the trip and money spent on it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;Ignite 2016 has finished and it was an intensive, useful great experience.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<link href="https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/fullLogBackup" />
		<id>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/fullLogBackup</id>
		<title>The transaction log for database 'Sharepoint_Config is full due to 'LOG_BACKUP'</title>
		<updated>2016-08-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;Well, if you or your customer doesn't have a good maintenance plan for your Sharepoint DB (Content &amp;amp; Configuration) you will someday face a situation where Sharepoint_Config transaction log grows tremendously or even fills your transaction log disk, so what to do?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: if you can't do any operation on the RDBMS (SQL Server) because the disk is full, you need either delete something on the disk (maybe a non important testing database) or expand the disk (if you are working on a virtual machine this is relatively easy).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you free enough space on the disk, you must to this in order:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set Recovery Mode for the Sharepoint_Config database to SIMPLE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shrink the Transaction Log FILES of the db&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set Recovery Mode for the Sharepoint_Config database to FULL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take a Full Database Backup!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to do the first 3 steps using T-SQL?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-sql"&gt;USE master;
ALTER DATABASE SharePoint_Config SET RECOVERY SIMPLE;
GO

USE [SharePoint_Config]
GO
DBCC SHRINKFILE (N'SharePoint_Config_log' , 1)
GO

USE master;ALTER DATABASE SharePoint_Config SET RECOVERY FULL;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you do this, you will see that Sharepoint Config database will shrink to a better reasonable size, but, it will grow again eventually so, my advice, create a maintenance job to do this before taking a full database backup.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;Well, if you or your customer doesn't have a good maintenance plan for your Sharepoint DB (Content &amp;amp; Configuration) you will someday face a situation where Sharepoint_Config transaction log grows tremendously or even fills your transaction log disk, so what to do?&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
</feed>