<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Andrés Gorzelany</title>
		<link>https://get-itips.capazero.net/</link>
		<description>Microsoft Solution Architect</description>
		<copyright>2018</copyright>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 17:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 17:38:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<item>
			<title>Script to call POSH-LTM-Rest cmdlets to enable or disable Pool Members on a F5 LTM Load Balancer</title>
			<link>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/ScriptPoshLTM</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<guid>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/ScriptPoshLTM</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had to do this PS Script for a customer, they use TFS and wanted to control F5 LTM (Load Balancer) to disable or enable nodes in a release definition,
so they can disable a node, update the binaries on it, and enable it again.
So, I found this excellent &lt;a href="https://github.com/joel74/POSH-LTM-Rest"&gt;Powershell modules&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href="https://github.com/joel74"&gt;Joel74&lt;/a&gt; that include the needed functions.
First of all, you have to install the POSH-LTM modules as the creator says on his github page on the computer that will be used to run the PS Script,
then, save this PS Script on the same computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt; param (
    [Parameter(Mandatory=$true)][string]$LTMName,
    [Parameter(Mandatory=$true)][string]$Partition,
    [Parameter(Mandatory=$true)][string]$PoolName,
    [Parameter(Mandatory=$true)][string]$MemberName,
    [switch]$disable = $false,
    [Parameter(Mandatory=$true)][string]$F5Username,
    [Parameter(Mandatory=$true)][string]$F5Password
)

$passwd = $F5Password
$user=$F5Username

$secpasswd = ConvertTo-SecureString $passwd -AsPlainText -Force
$ltmCreds = New-Object System.Management.Automation.PSCredential ($user, $secpasswd)


#Se solicita una sesion al F5 BIG-IP
$session = $null
$session = New-F5Session -LTMCredentials $ltmCreds -LTMName $LTMName -PassThrough

if($session -ne $null){
    if($Disable){
    Write-Verbose &amp;quot;Trying to disable $LTMName|$Partition|$PoolName|$MemberName&amp;quot;
    Disable-PoolMember -F5Session $session -PoolName $PoolName -Partition $Partition -Name $MemberName

    }else{
    Write-Verbose &amp;quot;Trying to enable $LTMName|$Partition|$PoolName|$MemberName&amp;quot;
    Enable-PoolMember -F5Session $session -PoolName $PoolName -Partition $Partition -Name $MemberName
    }
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go to the release definition of your project of choice, and add a &amp;quot;Powershell on target Machines&amp;quot; task, fill the fields as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Machines: fill with the hostname or IP of the computer with the PS Module and PS Script saved in the last step.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Admin Login / Password: Credentials to connect to this computer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protocol: HTTP or HTTPS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Powershell Script: Full path to the PS Script saved in the last step, for example C:\Scripts\F5Manage-TeamMember.ps1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Script Arguments: Arguments needed by my script, for example, using release variables:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-LTMName $(LTMName) -Partition $(Partition) -PoolName $(PoolName) -MemberName $(MemberName) -F5Username $(Username) -F5Password $(Password)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to create this variables in the release definition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Test it. always test it on your environment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Open Office Space is a fiasco</title>
			<link>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/open-office-fiasco</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;This time I took the liberty of talking about something that it is not IT related, but it is work related, here it goes:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<guid>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/open-office-fiasco</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This time I took the liberty of talking about something that it is not IT related, but it is work related, here it goes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some years now, we saw a new trend in offices, &amp;quot;let's remove the cubicles&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;let's remove the walls&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;this way, we can be more productive&amp;quot;.
Ok, the intention was good but, as a consultant that visits many companies I observed (and suffered) some things about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, you feel in a jungle, you hear multiple people talking, even on top of your own voice in your head, you loose focus if you need to concentrate, in this jungle, you will find people that is either yelling to someone on the phone, listening to their favourite music, making jokes to their partner or whatever that does not have anything to do with your job, so you maybe start to use headphones, a thing that is not always possible in every situation or if it is, the people on the office will surely start to think that you have some kind of social relationship problem, &amp;quot;hey, here comes that weird solo-guy&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another thing that happens in this jungle is constant interruption of your work: &amp;quot;hey, didn't send you an email because I saw you that we were in the same floor, please stop what you are doing right now and see my big little problem, come on, I also brought to you my notebook to your desk&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why? why office designers did you have to do this? did you even work in an office before? did you experience your great idea before releasing it to the world? or are you testing the beta version of it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not saying that we must return to the cubicle maze, but hey, let's find something in between of that, maybe we can have a more classic area and an open area in the same building so people can choose where they are more productive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My two cents on this. I really want to know what is your opinion&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Call failed to establish due to a media connectivity failure when both endpoints are...</title>
			<link>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/call-failed</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;internal&lt;br&gt;
external&lt;br&gt;
or one endpoint is internal and the other is federated or remote...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<guid>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/call-failed</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;internal&lt;br /&gt;
external&lt;br /&gt;
or one endpoint is internal and the other is federated or remote...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;any situation will do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was happening to me on an On-Premise deployment of Skype For Business (Front end and Edge Server) calling to Unified Messaging contact on Exchange Online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ICE Candidate negotiation was happening but eventually no &lt;code&gt;remote-candidates&lt;/code&gt; were negotiated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-cmd"&gt;ms-client-diagnostics: 22; reason=&amp;quot;Call failed to establish due to a media connectivity failure when both endpoints are internal&amp;quot;;UserType=&amp;quot;Callee&amp;quot;;MediaType=&amp;quot;audio&amp;quot;;MediaChanBlob=&amp;quot;NetworkErr=no error,ErrTime=0,RTPSeq=0,SeqDelta=0,RTPTime=0,RTCPTime=0,TransptRecvErr=0x0,RecvErrTime=0,TransptSendErr=0x0,SendErrTime=0,InterfacesStall=0x0,InterfacesConnCheck=0x0,MediaTimeout=0,RtcpByeSent=0,RtcpByeRcvd=0,BlobVer=1&amp;quot;;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this must be firewall-related, this is almost always firewall-related, it seems first that the NAT was maybe responding with another external IP from de ISP Pool, but that was ok, the rules were correct, we checked and re-rechecked, and after so many hours of troubleshooting with Snooper and Wireshark, we started to look more deeply on the firewall and tried weird things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The firewall, a Fortigate one, had a NAT button enabled on the rule, you would say, that is obvious that must be activated... but we tried and deactivated that and... Voilá! we saw the face of god at that moment, it worked, the remote-candidates were negotiated at that moment  (so always be sure that this line is present if you want to know that it is working ok)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-cmd"&gt;a=remote-candidates:1 65.55.127.80 54860 2 65.55.127.80 54721
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and we lived happily ever after.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Powershell Script to CSV all AD Permissions for a particular Receive Connector</title>
			<link>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/csv-adPerm</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<guid>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/csv-adPerm</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had to do this PS Script for me to troubleshoot a receive connector permissions problem.
This will output to a CSV all permissions assigned to a receive connector, please change the $path and $connector variables to suit your needs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;$path = &amp;quot;E:\path\dumpRights.csv&amp;quot;
$csv = &amp;quot;user,identity,deny,accessrights,extendedrights`r`n&amp;quot;
$connector=&amp;quot;connectorName&amp;quot;
$perms=Get-adpermission $connector

foreach($perm in $perms){
    $perm
    $csv+=$perm.user.RawIdentity+ &amp;quot;,&amp;quot; + $perm.identity.ToString() + &amp;quot;,&amp;quot; + $perm.deny.IsPresent + &amp;quot;,&amp;quot; + $perm.accessrights + &amp;quot;,&amp;quot; + $perm.extendedrights
    $csv +=&amp;quot;`n&amp;quot;
}

$fso = new-object -comobject scripting.filesystemobject
$file = $fso.CreateTextFile($path,$true)
$file.write($csv)
$file.close()
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Handy SMTP Handshake for testing with Telnet</title>
			<link>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/handy-handshake</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<guid>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/handy-handshake</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's always useful to test SMTP service, using Telnet, so these are the commands needed:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, connect through Command Prompt or Powershell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-cmd"&gt;Telnet x.x.x.x tcpPort
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Example &lt;code&gt;Telnet 10.0.2.1 25&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will get a welcome message from SMTP Server, like this one:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;220 exc02.contoso.com Microsoft ESMTP MAIL Service ready at Wed&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;then write sequentially hitting enter at each line what is coloured in green here (no color lines are server responses)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-code"&gt;EHLO mailtesting
AUTH LOGIN
334 VXNlcm5hbWU6
Y29udG9zb1xhY2NvdW50
334 UGFzc3dvcmQ6
dGhlUGFzc3dvcmQ=
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-code"&gt;MAIL FROM:
RCPT TO:
DATA
Subject: here comes the test 
This is the email content.
.
250 Queued mail for delivery 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important notes:&lt;/strong&gt;
You have to hit enter twice after subject input.
account name and password are entered Base64 encoded, so first encode that information using for example &lt;a href="https://www.base64encode.org/"&gt;this site.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How to succesfully import Root CA to Trend IWSVA</title>
			<link>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/import-ca-trend-iwsva</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Customer reached me to get help importing Root CA certificate to InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance,&lt;br&gt;
from Trend Micro documentation:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<guid>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/import-ca-trend-iwsva</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Customer reached me to get help importing Root CA certificate to InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance,&lt;br /&gt;
from Trend Micro documentation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="blockquote"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;By default, IWSVA acts as a private Certificate Authority (CA) and dynamically generates digital certificates&lt;br /&gt;
that are sent to client browsers to complete a secure passage for HTTPS connections. However, the default CA
is not signed by a well-known (trusted) CA on the Internet.Client browsers always display a certificate
warning every time users access an HTTPS Web site.
Although users can safely ignore the certificate warning, Trend Micro recommends using a signed root certificate for IWSVA.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, if you want your users not to receive a warning from their browsers you have to use, typical,an internal Certification Authority that all client computers trust, for example an Enterprise Windows CA like this was the case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, first of all, I had to export the CA Root Certificate including the Private Key,&lt;br /&gt;
go on and logon the Certification Authority computer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go to 'Start' -&amp;gt; 'Run' -&amp;gt; mmc.exe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on 'File' -&amp;gt; 'Add / Remove Snap-in'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click the 'Add...' button&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select 'Certificates' then click 'Add'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select 'Computer Account' -&amp;gt; 'Next' -&amp;gt; 'Local Computer' -&amp;gt; 'Finish'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;click 'Close' -&amp;gt; 'OK'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expand Certificates -&amp;gt; and click on 'Personal' -&amp;gt; 'Certificates'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Right click the CA cert and choose 'All Tasks' -&amp;gt; 'Export'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click 'Next' -&amp;gt; Select 'Yes, Export the private key' -&amp;gt; 'Next'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uncheck all of the options here. PKCS 12 should be the only option available. Click 'Next'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give the private key a password of your choice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give a filename to save as and click 'Next', then 'Finish'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that you have a .pfx file we will need to use the excellent tool called OpenSSL, as I was using Windows, I used OpenSSL for Windows binaries that you can get here &lt;a href="http://gnuwin32.sourceforge.net/packages/openssl.htm"&gt;http://gnuwin32.sourceforge.net/packages/openssl.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Install it and copy the pfx to your computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;start a command prompt or PowerShell and run:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-cmd"&gt;openssl pkcs12 -in -clcerts -nokeys -out certificate.cer
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;then&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-cmd"&gt;openssl pkcs12 -in -nocerts -out pkey-encrypted.key 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will end up with two files: certificate.cer and pkey-encrypted.key&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you import them right into IWSVA console it will fail saying &amp;quot;Root Certificate file is invalid. Try Again&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This drove me nuts, documentation is not so good, it only says you need to provide a PEM file format,  base54 encoded and RSA based encrypted key, and I was sure I was providing just that...  but wait... after many tries and errors, I read that some systems do not accept anything below this line in public certificate key file:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-code"&gt;-----BEGIN CERTIFICATE-----
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and this line for the private key file&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-code"&gt;-----BEGIN PRIVATE KEY-----
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;so I tried and deleted everything below that lines on both lines... and it worked! Apparently IWSVA can not handle well ignoring the information that comes there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope is useful for someone else.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Workflow Manager Re-Registration despite everything seems ok</title>
			<link>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/workflow-manager-error</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;So,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<guid>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/workflow-manager-error</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;So,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you did the exact steps and you receive the &amp;quot;Workflow is connected&amp;quot; message when you click on Workflow Manager Service Application inside Sharepoint Central Admin, but somehow, something is not working quite right, or maybe you receive this message trying to publish in Sharepoint Designer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/workflowmgr_error.png" class="img-fluid" alt="WorkFlow Manager Error" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Solution: Re-Register the Workflow Service using Register-SPWorkflowService and the -Force Parameter. There is a good chance everything starts working then.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How to limit download rate on Ignite Videos</title>
			<link>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/limit-dw-ignite-videos</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;If you are using &lt;a href="http://tomtalks.uk/2015/05/download-all-the-skype-for-business-ignite-sessions/"&gt;THE powershell&lt;/a&gt; script to download Ignite 2016 Videos and Slide Decks you probably noticed that it will try to use all your bandwidth available and maybe kill all your connections, so, if this happened to you, you will find this useful&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<guid>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/limit-dw-ignite-videos</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;If you are using &lt;a href="http://tomtalks.uk/2015/05/download-all-the-skype-for-business-ignite-sessions/"&gt;THE powershell&lt;/a&gt; script to download Ignite 2016 Videos and Slide Decks you probably noticed that it will try to use all your bandwidth available and maybe kill all your connections, so, if this happened to you, you will find this useful&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hack into the ps file, go to line 156:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;Start-Process -FilePath .\youtube-dl.exe -ArgumentList &amp;quot;-o &amp;quot;&amp;quot;$vidFullFile&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;, $url -NoNewWindow -Wait
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and replace with this&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-powershell"&gt;Start-Process -FilePath .\youtube-dl.exe -ArgumentList &amp;quot;-o &amp;quot;&amp;quot;$vidFullFile&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;--limit-rate 30K&amp;quot; , $url -NoNewWindow -Wait
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;customize the --limit-rate argument to suit your preferences and voila!&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>IGNITE 2016 IS GONE… LONG LIVE THE KING!</title>
			<link>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/ignite-2016</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Ignite 2016 has finished and it was an intensive, useful great experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<guid>https://get-itips.capazero.net/posts/ignite-2016</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Ignite 2016 has finished and it was an intensive, useful great experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you experienced the same as us, you can not get to all the sessions, the conference center was big enough to &lt;strong&gt;walk an average of 12 kilometers a day&lt;/strong&gt; (nearly 8 miles) and, I am not joking, it’s true, Google Fit told me everyday, so, the first day you get a little frustrated walking fast to go from one place to another, but the second or third day you realize the truth, and start to watch some sessions from hangouts or just sit anywhere and get the streaming using some headphones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, wait, what about if you couldn’t make it to Atlanta this year? no problem, or at least, you can get the juice of the sessions and slide decks using &lt;a href="http://tomtalks.uk/2015/05/download-all-the-skype-for-business-ignite-sessions/"&gt;this Powershell Script&lt;/a&gt;  to download them all (or maybe download the ones you are interested in), you can select the quality of the sessions too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lessons learned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As I told, you can not get to all the sessions, do not try, but, you have other options.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Try to avoid sessions on Expo, is a little difficult to hear the speaker as people walks by around you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner lead sessions are good to have real life situations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sessions lead by Microsoft Gurus like Jeffrey Snover and Mark Russinovich are a must-attend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use sneakers, you will have to walk A LOT&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do Networking, do it, talk to people, they do the same things as you do, they work on IT, it’s an excellent opportunity to share experiences and maybe to do business!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Ignite ends, your work starts, you will have to review what you have learned in the sessions, get deep on them and apply to your everyday work to grow your ITPro knowledge, maybe it’s a chosen certification path, maybe new solutions to offer to your customers, in other words, capitalize the trip and money spent on it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>